[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Billy Ray, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Ray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "So my first question is, did you ever have this terrible nagging feeling that if you suddenly keeled over from a heart attack tomorrow, the headlines would be, Miley Cyrus' dad dies of an achey breaky heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "If that were the case, that's what it's going to read.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "As you approach it, how would you sum up your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "YRUS: I would sum it up as, for every action, there is an opposite and equal reaction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "And as a musician all your life, does being able to have both extremes in your life, is that good for the creative process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I'd kind of like to know some vanilla.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "And when you see Miley occasionally falling off the straight and narrow, do you recognize that slightly rebellious edge to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What have you learned about yourself over the last 50 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I've learned that it's not how many times you get knocked down, it's how many times you get back up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 50 years?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "And what's the key to getting back on your feet when you've had a big blow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Dust yourself off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", ":", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What would you say have been the best and worst moments of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, the best -- the best being here with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "And what would you say had been the worst moment of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Oh, gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What would you least want to go through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What were his values that he tried to instill in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, first of all, he had a real love of music.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "If you ever think about it, ever wonder what he would have said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "JJR", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, I share that a lot with Miley, and with all my kids.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "When you watch yourself, though, what are you honestly thinking when you see yourself there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, I do look extremely happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "A year before that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "A year before that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "So you would have been, what, about 29?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WP", ",", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I was 29.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And what's the dream when you're in that car?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, the dream was and the prayer was that I would pray that God would give me the wisdom and the vision to sing the songs I was supposed to sing, to do the things I was supposed to do, to be the person I was supposed to be, and through my life and my music, I prayed that God would give me the ability to represent the light and his love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized this song was going to change your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, I had 10 songs recorded for the album.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ashland"], "LOCATION": ["Kentucky"]}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "When did you get a call or somebody said, you thought, wow, OK, this is going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "The night that we did the video in Ashland, Kentucky, that very nice, I felt like something changed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What happened when the teeter goes to totter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I got really busy, and started getting on a lot of airplanes and getting in a lot of limousines.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Well, you were on your own, weren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "It's what you felt, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I was definitely dealing with a lot in my world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "How did Miley actually react to the interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Shoot, I don't know, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "The next time you spoke to her, what did she say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "It was such a -- again, a dark time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "How can I stop you from having yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "You kids are my dream.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Knowing how many child stars in particular end up in a very dysfunctional way in their lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I just knew that there was a whole lot of change ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "TO", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Were you frightened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I couldn't really -- at that moment, you know, it's best to just -- you know if you hear the words of the song, you know, she's got to do what she's got to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Would you take that option?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Was it about me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "And underage drinking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Great clip, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It's amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What are probably the biggest misconceptions about your daughter, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "You know, I think that might be one in itself, is that -- she really -- she's the real deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "What is your -- looking back on it, a storm in a teacup?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Didn't see anything horribly wrong about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Were you surprised that people said they were inappropriate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Was the -- was the bong gate scandal worse for you to deal with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Bong gate happened in the midst of my darkness -- in my darkest hour.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "So you took it worse perhaps than you would have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "By then, I -- I was probably -- I was a bit numb of pain at that time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do you think she realized that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Not professionally, but are you proud of her for the way that she has dealt with these mini scandals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Oh, heck yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "And how is your relationship with her now, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "But since she's been famous, do you think you now have a stronger relationship than you've had before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I look back on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "WP", "NN", "IN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 565, "question": "And then what went right, when you look back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Well, I think when you look back on it, and you go, \"What went wrong?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "How did you -- how did you win your wife back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "You know, I just prayed for vision and strength, and wisdom to communicate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "I think it was more about step by step, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Given that the -- the -- this ride that you talk about, this rocket ride was part of the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "How have you adjusted things now so that it works better for all of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Communication is the key.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "So talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Everybody just talk at what's on your mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "When you got back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "I -- I'm guessing so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Yes, and I think probably -- did your mind flash back to how you felt as a five year old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "What does it stand for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110712pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "What does being an American mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "It's the land of the free, the home of the brave.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]